I want to break down for you right now
this webinar that I did recently that
converted at over
30% my name is Jason flatland everybody
considers me the greatest webinar
presenter of all time I certainly have
the track record to show for it you'll
actually see the proof Inception style
in this but let's break this down when
you start any webinar you want to hit
the ground running you got to do
something to hook people in get them
excited and it's even better if it's
kind of off-kilter like what's going to
happen next I've never had a frame of
reference for a webinar starting like
this for so that's what I try to do if
possible and in this particular case I
do this with a true false quiz so in and
of itself that's interesting and it
automatically creates interaction which
is really powerful to use on a webinar
but it does something very subtly
underneath of it every question attacks
an objection so one of the questions is
you got to be good at marketing to sell
info products and I give them an answer
so the answer helps them understand that
you you don't have to be an expert
marketer but marketing does serve a
function for info products so people are
generally in one of two camps I've
noticed they're either all expert no
marketing and they don't make any money
and they don't help anybody or they're
all marketing no expert and that's a
problematic challenge that only a
psychopath a narcissist or a sociopath
would be okay hey let me sell something
that isn't very good so I'm helping them
already kind of right fit I don't have
to be an expert marketer but there is a
style of marketing that I can learn and
apply very easily and I don't have to be
an expert by the way for an information
product to be published either and I
will demonstrate this this is what's
exciting if you have something really
powerful that you can show on a webinar
which is what you should aspire to then
you can make bigger claims the bigger
the impact you can make the bigger the
claim that you can pred it with and
what's exciting about webinars as
opposed to other types of advertising is
we get approve the claim in the webinar
traditional sales is I'm going to make a
claim you got to buy the product and
then hope the claim gets proven so I'm
going to lay the foundation that they
can learn the style of marketing if
they're not good at it that I'm going to
show them they don't have to be an
expert there's a way around it and in
fact in some cases it's better to not be
an expert I handle the objection of hey
there's all this free information out
there on YouTube and on podcast and so
on and so forth how it's an itch that
creates more scratching and the fact is
that the info business is 148 times
larger than was when I started which was
back in 2007 so I'm getting people
excited about that all the good product
ideas have been taken I hook into the
recency of AI at the time which is a
really hot thing and then the last thing
here is true or false speed is more
important than ever when it comes to
cashing in enormous profits waiting
online for you to claim as rightfully
yours this is very powerful what I'm
doing here I have learned that in almost
every single Market that you can
interact in people prefer a small win by
tomorrow as opposed to a bigger win 6
months down the road so most training
most teaching most education most
anything is this massively delayed
gratification yeah I get it that's how
most of the world works but it doesn't
always have to work that way I'm on a
Pursuit I am looking for that whale that
Moby Dick if you will on where is there
a case where there can be instant
gratification and I Prov that in this
webinar and I demonstrated and that's
what we've done here we've set it up and
this is a really important slide here
this is open Loops open Loops create
retention better than anything else that
you could do from a technique
perspective other than just be
interesting so interesting is the most
important thing and open Loops are the
second most important thing so I say on
this webinar you're discover how to
create a specific kind of high quality
info product in less than two hours that
automatically attracts buyers and sells
well even if you suck at marketing
here's the intended response to this
that I anticipate my audience will have
they'll say that's not even possible I
can't imagine that could ever be true
but on the off chance the one in the
million that it might be true I'm going
to stick around to see if he can prove
it and that creates this subtle frame if
he can prove it I'm going to be very
open to buying whatever he sells and in
fact I lean right into that I say my
promise I'm going to give you this and
if that's the case then I hope you
invest in what I offer at the end for
most people starting off the easiest way
to sell something is to tell people I
want to sell you this thing and here's
what I'm going to do for you first
before I sell it to you being completely
over not getting Fancy with it coming
right out and setting it up here's the
conditions in which I would like to sell
you this thing if we meet them then
you're going to be excited to know what
this thing is I want to sell you if we
don't meet them then please don't ever
entertain the idea of buying anything
from me that's the subtle frame that's
created there and that's really really
powerful and people are already like oo
I wonder what he's selling I can't wait
to see what he's selling now we do
definitions never assume that your
Market knows something that is key to
them getting a benefit out of what
you're teaching so I Define here what's
an information product then I show why
information products and this is where
you can hit the benefits I don't spend a
whole bunch of time on this one thing
you'll notice on this webinar is one
point per slide is the ideal I don't do
that as much on this webinar as I do on
other webinars because the price point
for the product that we're selling here
is
$499 now I want to show you how I
introduce myself on this webinar
whenever you're selling a webinar you
got to have the who am I and why you
should listen to me I try to spend as
little time on it as possible what is
the fewest things I can say that can
have the hugest like oh my God if
there's anybody to listen to on this
topic he or she is the person to listen
to I started and frame it with I've
created over a 100 information products
over the last 15 years I was a
millionaire before 30 multi-millionaire
soon after I've worked with
multi-billion dollar companies I did the
biggest internet marketing launch in
history and and then I show this
testimonial from Alex Heros here the guy
who sold more books on offers than any
anybody credits me with the single best
course he's ever seen on offer creation
that's really powerful and that's about
the real time of how I spend introducing
myself the thing about a webinar people
don't get is your best proof element of
who you are and why somebody should
listen to you is being interesting how
you Captivate somebody how you can show
them that you are the real deal and
you've thought about their problems more
than they have and it shows and how you
address them and communicate with them
will do far greater than anything you
could put on any number of slides now
people overcompensate that by putting
too much on slides and I get it I have
some of the most compelling insane proof
if you think about it because Zoom
brought me in I did the biggest launch
Alex Heros is probably the hottest name
in the space right now I have a
testimonial from him on the topic I get
that you probably don't have that I used
to not have that either so but you got
to think about the different ways you
can show your different proof elements
so they can have the biggest impact with
the least amount of time and it just
really kind of clears the air okay I get
it he's the expert so I should really
pay attention that's what you're
shooting for here now what's really cool
here is I've built myself up to this
massive thing which makes me completely
unrelatable to my audience so I have to
bring it back to reality and I say
before you make millions what turns your
life around is the first dollar you make
and I show the first product I ever sold
I have the screenshot show not tell show
as much as you possibly can tell as
little as you possibly can meaning that
the less slides that have all words or
if you're making claims the more you
have visuals on those claims the better
and now I get them very excited there's
also the implicit expectation that if
you continue to follow along you can
turn a small amount of success into a
large amount of success just like I have
done and then I give them the formula
one problem one solution one sitting
product creation Now when I reveal the
formula here I don't go immediately into
teaching it you want to get Buy in with
whatever you're going to teach before
you teach it get people leveraged have
tension around it so they're excited to
learn it so they say come on please
please please show it to me and then
we'll have more imp when you do show it
to them and so I set the framework I go
if you got a month to create it you
probably won't if you got a week if you
got a weekend the product needs to be
done when you sit down and when you
stand up it's finished that's the
Paradigm that I'm working on in this
webinar right here and notice I don't
just say it I romance it now so I come
back to the first product again one of
the things that you'll learn the more
you do this is it's better to take a
concept slice it up and then give it out
in chunks throughout the webinar since
it's a long form media what you do is
you find ways to unfold the story you
really have multiple story threads
running simultaneously and you're
putting this piece of the story in here
that piece of the story in there that
piece of the story in there so this is a
call back they've seen the screenshot
before now I'm adding a little bit more
Foundation to it before I didn't tell
them the name of the product now I'm
showing them the name of the product I
give them the anatomy of the product and
I get them excited about them I show
them the results about that I get them
pumped up cuz I I say on this slide here
I say even if I didn't get better and I
had a whole lot of room to get better I
knew if I just repeated the same thing
over and over again it would completely
change my life completely change my
finances and that speaks to the customer
because anybody who's really attending a
webinar has a low self-worth related to
whatever they're tuning in for and so
they think whatever you're going to do
they can only do one tenth or one/ 100th
of it so they're thinking worst case
scenario and you're selling best case
scenario so I'm always trying to C
celebrate to worst case scenario even
reading their mind hey but you're Jason
so you have some superpower that us mere
mortals don't now this is an interesting
thing too cuz I could have told this
story earlier on the who am I why am I
telling you this section but it goes
back to what I'm talking about of
slicing and dicing content and putting
it out in puzzle pieces so this is where
I tell the story that yes in fact I was
a rapping Monk and now I tell a little
bit more about my story The
personalization of it you don't become a
monk because life's going well it's
because things are very hard you show
where you came from you show what it
took to get there and you relate it back
to the audience and now I challenge the
audience a little bit here it's always
important to challenge the audience the
person that just caters and patronizes
to the audience is not going to get as
big of an impact as the person that
challenges so I say you need to have
some ambition you need to have some
Focus you need to have some desire and
I'm asking for commitment I say are you
up for that once you combine that with
this thing now I unpack a little bit
further I've introduced them to this
concept of one problem one solution one
sitting I've now repeated it a few times
and now I add to it present it in a
step-by-step format sell it at a low low
price here's what's interesting about
this this flies in the face of
everything else that they've been told
from every other Guru I'm telling them
to sell the things super cheap and not
to be concerned with maximizing profit
right now and being totally okay with
leaving some money on the table because
if you try to dress it all up it never
gets done that's my whole point my other
point is all the money is in the
existing customer list it's not in the
new customers but see most other people
don't want to tell tell them that cuz
they're afraid that would stop the sell
I'm using that to my advantage people
can see themselves more easily selling a
really cheap product and as a marketer
who's super successful I'm telling them
to sell a really cheap product it's very
interesting to them it gets more Rapport
in a way they normally you wouldn't get
and then I introduce a testimonial here
of a person I show the testimonial and I
and I point out to them something very
interesting which is paragraph 2 are
said I've already had the idea of what I
wanted to do for as long as 2 to 3
months but never got around to doing it
and I know subtly there's so many people
on this webinar that feel the same thing
that they have this great idea inside of
them and they just can't figure out a
way to get it out so I'm showing them
how this formula will get it out in the
easiest simplest form and then if it's
valid and people like it then they can
enhance it they can go further with it
they can do a whole bunch of stuff with
it but right now we want to take
something that's inside of them that
they're not making money with and get it
outside of them so they can make some
money with it and again this is always
going back to mind reading what is the
person thinking when I'm telling this
what is the potential objection excuse
ucer limitation that they would push
back on and they're scared hey well what
if I try this and it doesn't work and so
I frame that to them that hey if it
sells well great if it doesn't sell well
great because you can use it as an asset
you gain the experience it can be a lead
magnet it can be a bonus and if it does
okay great because you can stack a whole
bunch of okays together and still have
life-changing income and now they feel
very comfortable I've depressurize the
process it doesn't have to be great
which gets them off the hook and it
isn't great that's the reality really
good marketing is finding a way to align
the reality with the perception not to
pretend the reality is something that it
isn't because I know not everybody's
going to create a product that's going
to sell well and I'm flat out telling
them but I'm telling it to them in a way
that they will not stop them from doing
what they know that they want to do and
then this is where we break it down some
do better than others some flop some do
okay a few are huge home runs that can
change your life if you want to Stack
the deck in your favor to influence
having more home runs then these are the
four most important things now watch how
quickly I teach them each of these four
things here's the first thing better
than free I give them a definition try
to give a definition of what you're
going to teach in one sentence I give
them a jux to position so in this
particular case the point is if they did
it on their own it would cost them more
money than if they paid you for your
information product and again notice
there is some interaction which is the
better deal I'm asking the audience that
do this and it will literally cost them
more to not buy your product this is
called a tie down so you make the point
they get it and then you tie it down so
they can completely understand it and
then that's it so literally this is a
good framework if you're teaching
something introduce it give an example
tie it down great way to teach tactics
and now look at the second one here pain
before gain and I show them before you
saw the plan to Heaven provide the path
out of hell so this is why it's
important and then again ju to position
isn't that interesting who's likely to
spend more Joe Who Wants A Whiter
Brighter Smile so a better tomorrow or
Jane a crippling toothache the pain of
today and I get them to tell me people
will buy much quicker and at much larger
prices to get rid of an existing pain
that's a tie down three slides so why
it's important in this particular
instance jux to position tie down
instant gratification this is the third
thing this is really cool because it's
sort of meta I'm teaching instant
gratification and I'm leaning into it
further smaller results sooner are
better than bigger results later and
here's a big money-making secret now
this is where I spend a little bit more
time sometimes if you have a really cool
thing or if it you want to set it up
it's okay to spend a little bit more
time for the dramatic effect uh when you
reveal the point so big money making
secret you can take any how-to book gut
most of the content hone in on one thing
offer an immediate win now I show I
don't want to just tell if I have a
really powerful point it's better to
show it so here's a book it's 384 Pages
within this book that I personally
bought there's a single page more
specifically there's four steps on this
page it was an immediate game Cher for
me so I want you to imagine a scenario
now and look at the ju to position again
do people want a history lesson for $
that takes eight hours to consume or
would they prefer to buy a product
that's 10 pages long takes less than 20
minutes minutes to read and is about the
same price what's easier to sell what's
easier to create so this is jua position
with an interactive device there and
this really makes people feel
comfortable and Justified because I know
right now the skepticism of if I create
these one problem one solution one
sitting products are they really
valuable they're very thin and people
have trouble differentiating between
quantity and quality so this is how I
help them see that with this example and
then hypers specific the more you tailor
Solutions so this is the definition
again right I show them my example here
and then I show them other examples one
is a product E-class student one ties
back to the earlier example of me being
a monk and then I tease them with this
New Concept which is just I find very
interesting I say these people make
thousands of dollars per month selling
live Roaches on eBay they would make
tens of thousands of dollars teaching
others how to do it as well and that
gets people excited so I didn't tie it
down in this sense because I'm
immediately going to move into the close
they say regardless if you're an expert
of renew this is the best way to do that
and now I show an example of a
testimonial who took the course I show
another example of a testimonial who
took the course I show a third quick
example I show a fourth quick example
and then I start to close now this is a
famous close I've taught this to a lot
of people and it works in almost really
any scenario where you're selling
information I say I could go on and on
people just like you did it does that
mean you can do it and then I say no I
say probably not to be specific and this
is a great pattern interrupt because
people are so used to be imp pandered to
when they're sold I can do it so you can
do it they did it you can do it so I
want to do a fake out I want people to
feel like they got it and then say well
hold on you can't do it so I'm creating
tension I'm actually creating a problem
which then I have a solution for this is
the transition from content to close
here I say if we part a ways right now
would you go out immediately set the
world on fire with your new found
product creation skills doubtful so I'm
leaning into it further because the
reality is I know no matter what
training I could give them in 45 to 60
to 75 minutes or even 90 or 120 Minutes
is not going to change habits it's silly
and absurd that people pretend that such
a thing actually exists so why not
affirm the truth in the most impactful
way possible you'll get the deepest
report and I say I probably know you
better than you know yourself you're
stubborn and if I let you you will
quickly default back to your old habits
which are not making the money that you
deserve and then I say that's why I
won't let that happen so I've now
positioned the fact that I'm selling
them something a useful thing which it
is it's crazy why would you sell
something to somebody that isn't a
useful thing and if it is a useful thing
why would you not let them know that I
don't understand anyway I say that's why
I won't let that happen you need me in
your ear more than today if you're truly
going to take what I showed you on this
webinar and turn it into piles of cash I
like to take a very straightup approach
if you haven't noticed this at this
point in time people want to make a
bunch of money yeah they want to change
the world yeah they want to help others
but the nub of it is they have a small
bank account they want a large Bank
account so I call it as it is very
directly but I'm also calling in the
sense that they won't form a new habit
or a new Behavior pattern on one webinar
they need repetition they need support
they need additional help beyond what I
could just give them freely one session
one time and I say best of all if you
don't quickly make twice your investment
with my product creation Secrets will
give you double your money back so now
I'm teasing and interesting part of this
offer better than money back guarantees
are some of the most effective way ways
you can sell anything and they're very
rare almost nobody does them yes I get
it it's hard to figure one out um
there's risk involved for you if you do
it right because if your product sucks
you may end up paying out more money
than you took in so start small and test
on a very small scale the more risk
you're willing to incur on behalf of
your prospects the more prospects you'll
turn into customers so I'm using a
double your money back guarantee in this
instance and I'll show you what that
looks like more here in a bit and then I
introduce the product now the
interesting thing is this is 5.0 which
I'm not a fan of people like new tried
and true even establish and all that
good stuff it's harder to sell than a
brand new thing but the reality is I've
been doing this training in some way
shape or form now going on 15 years so
there's something to be said about the
longevity of this course and this is the
fifth version that I've taught from the
ground up and we released this a little
bit earlier this year in 2023 so product
eClass now look at how little time I
spend on what's in the course itself and
then look at how much time I will spend
on the bonuses I introduced the product
but I don't immediately dive into it I
set this stage so somebody could
understand how great the product is with
this Slice of Life story I say here's
where I got started in this little shed
here in Corville Iowa where my living
room was my office was my bedroom I
couldn't fit both a desk and a bed in
there so I slept on the floor so I'm
telling them a story about me in a time
I had to make a sacrifice and they can
now step into those shoes and see
themselves having to make a sacrifice of
time and money in order to better
themselves and the story continues what
made the difference was when I had my
first big investment to work with the
right Menor who gave me no other option
but to succeed and I want to extend that
beautiful gift to you as well so I
showed them that it's a really smart
idea to pay somebody else to help you
even if the payment is a lot of money
and it's painful to make the payment I
put myself into their shoes I remember
the first ever high ticket course I
bought it was a $2,000 course and and
the guy I was working for at the time I
was painting houses I called him up
because I didn't have a credit card to
charge it on and they had no alternative
method I said hey come over to my shed
in Corville Iowa which he did put it in
there and I'll pay you back I'll write
you a check that's how I had to buy my
first course that was the position I is
in and I didn't have a bed at the time I
did sleep on the floor and then now I
show what's in the course I explain what
it is so I have one slide that kind of
gives the snapshot overview of what it
is I break down each session so it has a
SE headline has a a couple really
powerful bullet points and a screenshot
of one slide in the course and I do the
same thing with session two this one has
only three bullet points session three
same thing session four just two bullet
points session five and there's all our
sexy title one two to three to four to
five bullet points one cool imagery from
within the course itself same thing with
session six in this case I use a proof
element usually it's preferable to use
proof elements attached to it so it's
sexy title couple bullet points reason
why it's a bonus proof element tie it
down in terms of how valuable it is with
a price anchor it should be this much at
yours free that's the best procedural
way to do bonuses since this product is
lower ticket it's only about 500 bucks I
don't even go that far although
reviewing this now I think maybe I
should and then here's session seven
same formula so we blow through that it
takes maybe three minutes to give them
the whole feel on here's what it is
here's what it does here's what you get
here's how you get it and that's this
slide here and then I start to do the
price drop price anchoring basically is
you start at a high thing and then you
lower it to a very low thing I think
it's somewhat cheesy but every time I've
not used price anchoring I've converted
less than when I have used price
anchoring so I use it so how much
successful people have made five figures
so charging five figures would make s
when I do my in trining seminars they
cost $5,000 about notice the proof
element normal price to the public is
this and if you look at it this is not a
pitch to sell product E-class to you
here today this is just showing you how
the sausage gets made and it is that is
the regular retail price if you can get
on one of my webinars in the rare few
times or an affiliate webinar where we
run these then we do run time limited
offers every webinar should have some
special offer to it should have some
sort of discount and some sort of
additional bonuses the best way to do a
webinar so I give them a Time limited
special offer in this case $4.99 one
time or 194 three installments I try not
to use the word cost or pay sounds and
feels better if it's $4.99 one time or
194 thre monthly installments and then
you do your first call to action and
then in my opinion is when the real
selling starts because I then start to
build on the bonuses so we put the price
up front put the value in the back we
call this mullet technique offer and
price short in the front bonus in the
value long in the back and now check out
this bonus Stacks so bonus number one
101 killer product topics the purpose of
this bonus is to eliminate the objection
well G Jason I don't know what to sell I
don't know if I'll ever come up with an
idea and so that is the primary and sole
purpose of this bonus is to kill that
objection bonus number two AI product
creation secrets and so because AI is
the hottest coolest thing right now you
should have some sort of bright shiny
object in your bonus package for no
other reason than it would be
inconspicuous in its absence this thing
must not be fresh and must not be
cutting edge if he has this huge
Omission in it that everybody else is
talking about so that's bonus number two
bonus number three marketing software
Secrets this shows them all the tech
that they would have to use in order to
sell a product online and people are so
weirded out about the tech it is a huge
objection so this is another objection
killer now we don't tell them the
platform and the software outright we
don't say hey use cart
we will show you step byep how to use
cartra the main reason why is because in
the future we might change that so it's
better to be flexible here and then have
to go back and redo every single thing
that built up to it but we're
positioning it as we'll show you exactly
how to run the technical stuff bonus
number four templates these are just
Sizzle it's uh the icing on the cake it
gets people excited because it shows
them how they can do things that are
normally hard very easily so this is
just taking additional resources like
sales templates bullet point templat
templates interview question templates
content cheat sheet as a template given
it to them I could have just shipped it
in the course but it's cooler to pull it
out and make it its separate thing bonus
number five is is a nice bonus technique
that you can use my friend in alumni in
my Mastermind my $25,000 Mastermind at
Driven Rachel Miller is her name and she
has a course that she doesn't really
sell it anymore but it retails for
$99.97 so she's not out there pushing it
and trying to sell it but the course is
that's what it cost and it's really good
for traffic from an organic s
perspective which I don't do and I'm not
good at but I can now put that in here
so this helps them see themselves yet
another way for them to get traffic
above and beyond because otherwise they
think if I can create an info product
but not get traffic then I'm screwed and
they won't buy so thirdparty bonuses and
I don't have to pay anything for this
just work out a deal hey can I include
it in in this case she says yeah she
just wants the exposure what a cool way
to get a bonus huh that's bonus number
five now here's the the real big bonus
it's resell rights to three of my
products so then I can say 100% of my
people who take product E-class have a
product and I mean I don't ham it up and
really lean on it and push it uh because
I feel like that would be deceptive but
the idea here is is these are valuable
because people can see themselves using
the marketing techniques even if they
don't create their products on products
that I will give them and they are super
high quality products I don't show them
anymore because we change them and we
add more from it from time to time so
from a scalability perspective but back
in the day I used to show the products
then I used to show the funnels as well
so they get the products and they get
wholes funnels and we also position it
as this is good practice for you so you
can go through the ins and outs of
setting up a product online before you
even create your first product so it's a
very sexy bonus and then bonus number
seven this is called a conditional bonus
it's always nice to have a conditional
bonus because then you can offer
something even more outlandish than what
normally you could on a bonus and this
is a consult with me and they have to
sell $10,000 first before they can book
a consult with me this is a a great way
to get testimonials by the way so it
helps incentivize people to be
successful and then when you talk to
them you learn their story and can use
it as a testimonial later very powerful
stuff and then I always link bonuses on
webinars they're exclusive so if you
went to the main website you would see
it costs twice as much for the product
and it doesn't come with any bonuses
this is they get a half off and they get
all these bonuses call to action slide
always should have one when you do a
webinar where you at a glance if you
could only have one slide to show
everything that you sell this would be
it notice the biggest font on here is
the URL they would go to that URL is not
functional anymore that was for a a
private webinar that we did for a client
and then the double your money back
guarantee so when they go to the URL we
have all the details listed it's super
easy to comply with the guarantee it's
like create a Google Document document
what you do for that day do that for 60
days straight and then if you haven't
doubled your money back we'll give you a
double your money back and I there's one
other condition you actually have to set
up a product and do a test payment to
verify that somebody could purchase the
product I'm talking ridiculously low
barrier of Entry because often what
separates people from success or not is
the first step most people just
psychologically can't commit to that
first step so the double your money back
guarantee helps conversion obviously
because it reduces risk but it also if
you do it right increases people's
success which which is why I love a
double your money back guarantee in this
case we have the regular guarantee on
top of that as well so for any reason or
none at all they want their money back
they can get it and then we talk about
support which kind of lends into people
feeling like yeah well what if you
promise that you'll give me my money
back and then disappear so this kills
that feeling right there uh one more
kind of inspirational shove into the buy
button which is like look at how big
this is you want to get in on this and
then I frame it as well look what I've
done I'm your guide I'll get you there
and then this is something recently so
for Alex her Mo's book launch he paid me
$25,000 to consult with him and then
back to the call the action slide and
then what we do from here on out with
live webinars is we just handle
objections and we answer questions and
we'll spend another hour or two or three
in some instances depending on how many
people are on the webinar now we have an
automated version of this as well and
that works really good and what we'll do
in that instances is we know kind of the
general questions people ask so we'll
answer that but we don't pretend hey
Sarah said blah blah blah none of that
nonsense or goofiness we just go more
impersonal here's some of the things
that you may be thinking that could
influence whether you would say yes to
this or no to this so here's the first
thing and then we would talk about that
and speak extemporaneously on that but
this is a great webinar for most people
to model I feel because it's so
straightforward there's not a lot of
moving parts to it and I
think